Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things.
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see!
What sort of form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're waiting!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look to the wind to dry all the tears!
As you're braving the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
Oh, my God.
You're going to toss this
in the water or what?
I think you need to learn
your own limitations.
Stand firm!
Throw them overboard!
What's that?
It's Team Faye!
Behold my Fishman Karatis!
Watch your aim.
Oh, we were going to use
that ship, weren't we?
Once I enter the water, I'm
afraid my strength runs wild.
Even if you made it outside, there's
no ship for you to escape on.
Don't do it, Straw Hat!
This is over the limit!
Run for your life!
Champion!
It had a good run, but my
wax can't help you anymore!
No more!
What? What?
Scary!
Now perish.
Venom demon!
We better run!
Yeah, you think?
Hell's judgment, die!
He got me!
Please don't leave me! Help!
No, dammit, don't touch me!
Why would I have some clothes?
It looks like it's not just my wax!
That poison is spreading
over everything it touches!
Like a tidal wave of very bad news!
It was cool while it lasted me!
Yeah, that does look pretty bad!
Hurry up, straw boy!
You gotta make it!
What about the ships?
I can hear gunfire, but the fog's
too heavy to make out anything.
This is driving me crazy, man!
I know they're plenty
capable of stealing a ship,
but if the Marines delay them
long enough, we're screwed.
Sounds like they're pretty far out.
Even if they do nab a ship,
they'll have to drag it all the
way back here for us to get on it.
No way!
Magellan's probably going to
catch up to us any minute now.
I know Straw Hat survived
a fight with him once,
but nobody can stop Magellan,
and this is taking awfully long.
Straw Boy!
Teen Bay, hurry!
We're counting on you!
Do them all!
Don't let them take the ship!
Did his arm just turn into a knife?
What's up with this guy?
It's the Diced Ice Fruit.
I remember that bastard!
He's an assassin from the West Blue!
It's only a matter of time
before they take that ship!
I refuse to suffer that dishonor!
Have the cannon sink it, sir!
Ready, cannon!
Oh no, not again?
The gunpowder!
It's so Jinbei, huh?
Keep him locked down.
Open fire!
He's right behind us!
We gotta run faster!
Jinbei?
Hey, you there, we're coming!
I hear straw boy!
Run for it!
I don't know what that
thing is, but holy crap!
It's Magellan!
No, we're all gonna die!
Did you get a ship?
Not yet!
We can't tell what the
heck's going on out there!
What?
Hell, a wing!
Is that Eva?
Don't scare us like that!
Oh, I made it.
Yay, it's nappy time.
No, not nappy time.
You have a head injury.
Thank goodness, you're alive.
I was so scared, I can't lose you!
Still breathing, are you?
Hey, Straw Hat, call from Jinbei!
A baby transponder snare?
Excellent work, gentlemen!
Now you show up.
Luffy, you reached the exit?
Uh-huh, but Magellan's still after us!
We're kind of running
out of places to run!
I see.
It took a while, but we do have a ship.
We'll be there soon, but
I need you to trust me.
Just keep running.
Jump straight into the water.
That goes for you and
all of the prisoners.
Are you out of your mind?
You realize this is the clone belt, right?
Sorry, but I don't have
time to explain right now.
Let's do it!
What?
Three, I need another
wax thingy. We're dead!
Either we drown or Medela destroys us!
Why do you trust that fish man anyway?
He's a warlord.
He's probably trying to curry
favor with the government.
He's his friends are my friends, too.
He won't let us down.
Into the water? Go ahead.
Let the Sea Kings eat you and save me
the trouble of cleaning up the mess.
Be careful!
Even a drop of that poison will kill you!
I got a beat!
Help!
Judgment once more!
For dear!
This is as big as I can make it!
One candle wall coming right up!
I got enough of your nonsense!
Help! Help! Help!
Jaaaa!
Whoa!
They pushed him back!
The poison is still seeping through!
Do we gotta dive into the water after all?
We did!
Hey, Eva! Wake up! Hurry!
We're in big trouble!
I need your fat head to do something!
I'm all tiny right now, and
you're the strongest person here!
What's that?
We've got to get out of here!
Who are you, baby straw boy?
Do the wing thing!
Do it! Okey-doke. No!
Please! All right! Help!
Here we go!
Wade, you're not in your right mind!
There's no way that's their plan.
They won't survive two minutes in those
waters without a ship, and they know it.
Everybody grab onto
Eva's face! Do what? No!
Whatever you're trying to do, stop it!
Hold on!
Help me!
I said stop!
We're falling!
Something huge is under the
ship a swarm of sea kings.
We landed on something
look down i can't believe
this how are we still
alive i'm glad you made it.
You must forgive me for making such
an outlandish request back there.
It's a school of whale sharks!
Jim Bay must have called them!
Ha-ha-ha!
Awesome!
Now that is handy!
Ha-ha!
All right!
Yee-haw!
Take that stupid poison guy.
She can't be fun too.
No more and fell down torture.
And I think I had almost given up hope!
It's not time to celebrate yet.
We still have a struggle ahead?
We won!
Thanks guys!
You whale sharks are awesome.
I'll never forget you!
You saved our lives.
I'd better start treatment on Inazuma.
See what they've got
stashed in the sickbay.
Right.
I'm never going back to that
hellhole as long as I live.
Yeah, man, no more crime.
I'm heading home to be a family man.
Suck it, diarrhea man.
We're finally free.
That's right, you're free.
And thanks to who?
Say it loud!
Captain Buggy!
Resilient little insects. Come in.
This is Warden Magellan.
Bring me a ship.
I can still chase them down. Yes, sir!
Little do they know, for all their joy,
they've merely leapt from one
cage straight into another.
Rear Admiral, sir!
We have repaired the battery that was
damaged by Koby in the last battle.
Good work.
All ships, let's open fire!
They're gonna sink us!
This is no way to die!
Come on, you guys, just let us go!
They've got a whole fleet!
We're dead!
We've done well enough so far,
since all of their high-ranking officers
have been summoned to Marine Corps.
But we're still outnumbered, and
they won't let us go so easily.
Can't you see how I see your time?
For filthy criminals such as you,
the Gates of Justice will never open!
Oh crap!
I forgot about that thing!
We're going to crash right
into it! He can't! Yeah!
Go Dancer!
Whatever that guy said!
Hey, come on now!
What are we gonna do now, shark?
Keep sailing!
You have lost your damn mind!
You trying to get us killed?
Why the hell are you so calm?
We're all about to die!
Protect the ship.
The gate can come next?
Why are we putting up with this crap?
This is a navy ship too!
Fire back, you imbeciles!
I was just about to see
that on the cannons.
Men, give them hell.
Roger that, Captain Foley!
Take this! Save us!
I'm gone! Balloon!
Look on that! Fire!
Where do they think they're going?
They expect the gate to
just open like magic.
Yeah, good luck with that.
Magellan would have to hit
the switch for them himself.
Guess the poor fools missed
the memo on that one.
And fire!
Don't stop to their song!
The Gates of Justice! They're opening!
But why?
This doesn't make sense!
Contact Impel Down!
It's opening!
Why is this happening?
A trap!
I don't know what's
going on and I don't care
as long as we're not dead and I can save
these! It's open! It's open! It's open!
They're escaping! Thanks!
Warden Magellan, hurry, please!
No, wait.
The gate.
Who authorized this?
You're sure you want to open the
Gates of Justice at a time like this?
Warden Magellan, sir?
Of course I am.
Do you have any reason to doubt me?
No, I suppose not.
As soon as the prisoner's ship makes its
way through, I want you to close the gate.
Understood?
If you say so, sir.
We haven't lost them
yet. Take the ship. Fire!
Did Magellan order this?
What's he thinking?
Has anyone contacted the ward?
Something isn't right here.
Actually, sir, I agree.
We saw the warden at
the pier a moment ago.
The thing is, he seemed as confused about
it as we are and just took off running.
When I find out who's responsible
for this, I'm gonna wring their neck.
Damn it, control room!
What are you doing?
Who told you to open the gate of justice?
Wait, a warden?
All this time you knew and that's why
you didn't stop you bastard that's me!
I got you you silly man
didn't learn your lesson
the first time did you
he was a fake all along?
Look!
They're trying to close the gate on us!
That's good.
As long as we can make it through in
time that it'll slam in their faces,
then we'll be free to go!
Damn it!
Vaughn was with us just a second ago!
He helped us fight Eva,
and he helped us escape!
He saved me from that poison and
cheered for me the whole way!
He's my friend, and you
want to go without him?
There's no time!
We can't just leave him to die back there!
You listen.
The only way anyone could make it,
we've left immeasurable comrades behind.
Do you want to go back and fight Magellan
again and risk losing even more friends?
What if we hadn't stayed
behind to open the gate?
Then where would we be right now?
Dead or worse?
If anyone can get the gate
open for you guys, it's me.
Don't worry, your pretty little blue head.
I don't doubt that you can
succeed, but then what?
Let's not ask silly questions, all right?
But do me a favor and don't tell
Strawboy until communications are cut.
Swans never die and never say goodbye.
It's still connected.
Baby transponder snails
have limited coverage.
Once the gate closes, you
won't be able to speak to him.
You dare to mark the warden?
You'll pay for this!
I knew memorizing your
face was a good idea.
Wake up, you imbecile!
What the hell happened here?
Please, you're choking me!
And touch. Watch!
Curse you!
God! God!
Strawboy? Hey!
Can you still hear me?
It's Luffy!
Are you nuts?
Why are you doing this?
It's just like last time!
Jibe, you promised you weren't
far to tell him until later!
This is the last thing I wanted!
We were supposed to break
out together, weren't we?
Damn it!
How many times do you
have to save me, huh?
I was there! Say something! Answer!
He saved us.
We're only free now.
Because he stayed behind in that
hell. Come on! Brother, please!
We just want to talk to you!
Let us know you're alive, okay?
Say something!
Run!
Mr. Two!
Oh, dare you, Mr. Two!
Before I can tell you, I'm sorry!
Ha-ha!
Bond boy! Fire!
Don't let them get through that gate!
Blow them to smotheries!
Bond!
It made me!
This is it.
The gate's about to close.
We have to go.
So thank you.
We'll never forget you!
Strawboy! I'm here!
Strawboy!
Five days! Save him!
And don't look bad!
I know you can do it.
And you have lots of friends.
To help you.
The gate is closing.
Keep hiring!
Take them out.
Did you miss me, old pal?
No!
Yeah, we did it!
We really did it!
Oh, stop pulling my tail!
Strawboy, I've come here to rescue you!
In the name of our everlasting friendship!
Hang in there!
You have to live!
Strawboy!
Swans never die and never say goodbye.
Rawr!
I can't believe this.
Take out a way!
We owe him our lives.
We're finally free.
If it wasn't for him, we'd be sitting
at the bottom of the ocean right now.
Even in the depths of hell, the flower
of friendship shall still bloom,
flames licking at its stem.
And on the sands of the river
where souls part from the living,
it sheds a solitary petal,
leaving it behind as a memento.
So let us vow that we shall
make it bloom again someday.
Oh, come my way!
Any last words before I eliminate you?
Have at me!
Let us meet again in the
garden of O Come My Way.
And suddenly,
in one fell swoop,
the number of prisoners that had escaped
from Impel Downjump from 1 to 241.
And yet,
this is only the beginning of a turn of
events that will shake the entire world.
The public execution of Portgas D.
Ace will take place in four hours.